Purgatory is a fantasy, western, tv movie film directed by Uli Edel.
An outlaw band flees a posse and rides into Refuge, a small town
where no one carries a gun, drinks, or swears.
The town is actually Purgatory, and the peaceful inhabitants are all famous dead outlaws and criminals such as
Doc Holiday and Wild Bill Hickok who must redeem themselves before gaining admittance to Heaven...
or screw up and go to Hell.
Sheriff Forrest / Wild Bill Hickock, played by Sam Shepard.
Blackjack Britton, played by Eric Roberts.
Doc Woods / Doc Holliday, played by Randy Quaid.
Cavin Guthrie, played by Peter Stormare.
Leon 'Sonny' Miller, played by Brad Rowe.
Deputy Glen / Billy the Kid, played by Donnie Wahlberg.
Purgatory, also known as Purgatory West of the Pecos, is a 1999 American
Western fantasy television film directed by Uli Edel.
The film premiered on TNT on January 10, 1999.
It focuses on a gang of outlaws who find their way to a hidden valley and a peaceful town, where residents
shun swearing, alcohol, guns, and any kind of violence, but resemble dead Western heroes.
The outcome is marked by its exploration of the interface
between legend-making and humanitarian values.